

# **Federico Perrone**

DNI 36139465 14/09/1991 (30 years) - Single.

Pedro Goyena, 1504. Los Naranjos NBH. 5010 Córdoba (Córdoba), Argentina.

+54 9 351 7526757

fedeperrone@gmail.com | fede\_perrone@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/fedeperrone

# **Computing Skills**

Java

HTML5

CSS3

C#

**JavaScript** 

**SQLite** 

**SQL Server** 

MySQL

Office / OpenOffice

Linux

# **Interests**

Game Development Software Development

#### Languages

English
Advanced level.
First Certificate in English,
University of Cambridge, 2009.

### **High School**

Colegio Jesús María.

Bachelor in Natural Sciences,
Health and Environment.

2009 GRADUATE, CÓRDOBA.

# **Personal Summary**

My goal was and will always be to continuously grow personally and professionally, as well as adding value to the organization.

I seek to be a part of a kind and honest work environment, where partnership, peer teaching and mentorship from the most experienced is encouraged.

I've applied different technologies in small web, android and desktop academic projects using Java, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript (vanilla), SQL and SQLite. I'm also currently studying and practicing with C#, SQL Server.

Studies include subjects such as systems analysis methodologies, systems design, requirements with agile methodologies, UML, testing theory, Scrum, networking basics, Windows and Linux user.

#### **Formation**

# Instituto Superior Santo Domingo.

Higher Technical Degree in Software Development. MARCH 2019 - PRESENT, CÓRDOBA. Ongoing Studies. ISSD.

# Universidad Tecnológica Nacional.

Mechanical Engineering.

FEBRUARY 2012 - DECEMBER 2015, CÓRDOBA.

Incomplete Studies. UTN FRC.

# **Professional Experience**

ADC Tecnología, Specialized Salesman.

JUNE 2017 - PRESENT, CÓRDOBA.

Digital business manager, Tekcenter.com.ar.

Commercial advisor, Account Executive.

Purchases, Sales, Technical Advisory.

Digital marketing team coordination.

Systems Analysis, Selection and implementation.

# Fepicor SA, Specialized Salesman. NOVEMBER 2015 - JUNE 2017, CÓRDOBA. Sales, Purchases, Stock, Technical and Commercial Advisory. Fundación Civil Casa del niño, Support Teacher. APRIL 2013 - APRIL 2014, UNQUILLO, CÓRDOBA. Support Teacher in Maths, Physics and Chemistry.